Guide to the Elizabeth S. Lyman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-1990-096
  - WAF/CP International, Series 9
    - WAF/CP Women's Research and Education Institute (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Hub Women's Technical Institute (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Wonder Woman Foundation (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Fdn. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Ruth Zambrana Hispanic Women's Network (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP General Organization 80-81 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP 4/5-6/83 Sixth Annual Meeting (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Board Meeting, 1/31/1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Board Meeting - New York, 1/31/1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Board Meeting, 11/15/1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Board Retreat - August 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - WAF/CP Networks, Series 10
    - WAF/CP Regional Networks Committee March 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Regional Development Committee (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Research Comm. 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Ann DeBusk (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Donor Technical Assist. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - WAF/CP Conf. Internship Group (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Job Descriptions (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP Suburban Propane Gas (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP Women's CV's 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP Women's CV's 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Teenage Pregnancies (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Networks - Boston (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Permanent Charity Fund - Boston Network Meeting (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - WAF/CP Networks Chicago (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - WAF/CP Networks Cleveland (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - WAF/CP Networks Denver (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - WAF/CP Networks General (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - WAF/CP Networks - Kansas City (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - WAF/CP Networks Minnesota (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - WAF/CP Networks New York (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - WAF/CP Pittsburgh Network 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - WAF/CP Pittsburgh 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAF/CP Networks S.E. Council on Foundations (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Northern California Fdns. Meeting 6/21/79 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - WAF/CP Networks San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - WAF/CP S.F. BAWIP Luncheon 4/3/80 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - WAF/CP S.F. Forums Network 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - WAF/CP S.F. BAWIP - Irvine Networks (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - WAF/CP Networks Seattle (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - WAF/CP Networks Twin Cities (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2000-074
  - National Network of Women's Funds Conference 3/22-25/1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Women & Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy 4/25-26/1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Council on Foundations Meeting 3/1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association of Black Foundation Executives Meeting 3/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fannie Mae Annual Report, Maxell Award (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Foundation Long Range Planning Committee 7/9-10/1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Director Meeting Agenda 3/8/1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board biographies 7/1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Financial Review & Audit Committee, 7/1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 7/24/1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Foundation Publications (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - California Civil Rights Initiative packet 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, Articles, Memoranda (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pew Annual Report 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Eshoo for Congress 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Women Leadership & the Future 5/29/1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Independent Sector 10/1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - John Gardner Fellowship Applicant Review 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 5/6/1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Correspondence, Notes (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Business Plan 11/1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Directors Meeting 6/6/1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - East Palo Alto Community Development Partnership 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Packard Foundation Annual Report 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Enterprise Foundation Correspondence, publications (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Enterprise Foundation Publications (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Statements & Audit 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Enterprise Foundation Business Plan Draft Review 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 7/9/1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Enterprise Foundation Executive Committee & Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 10/1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/15/1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 1/1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Enterprise Foundation Correspondence, Notes, Memoranda, Publications (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 10/24/1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Consumer Report Travel Letter 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Consumer Report Travel Letter 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lyman Book Fund Notecards (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Publications (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Council on Foundations Conference 5/1-3/1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Aspen Institute Quarterly 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bhumika Herbal Diary 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation Conference 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Publications (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Women's Foundations/Corporate Philosophy packet 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Phyllis Chesler Correspondence 5/1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - IBM Investments 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N (American Leadership Forum/National) Kellogg Foundation 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Women's Funding Network Conference 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Council on Foundations Conference 3/1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Corporation for Enterprise Development Conference 6/24-26/1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AEO (Association for Enterprise Opportunity) Microenterprise 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Foundation Report Drafts (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Women & Philanthropy 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Women's Funding Network/ Women & Philanthropy Conference 4/4-26/1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Trip – Microcredit 2/1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee 11/1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 11/6/1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Director's Meeting 11/6/1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Senior Ventures Memoranda (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - City of Palo Alto Proclamation of Lifetime Achievement for Jing Lyman 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Foundation Social Investment Corporation packet (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation packet (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Foundation Jubilee packet (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 11/3-8/1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Independent Sector Trip 11/2-4/1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - James Rouse Forum on the American City 6/24/1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Foundation Publications 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - AEO Trip 5/1-4/1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Conference on Entrepreneurship 3/7-8/1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Responsible Wealth packet 2/1999 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Council on Foundations Conference 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Cooperative Home Care Associates packet 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ALF/N Trip 4/29-5/1/1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Independent Sector Conference 10/17-19/1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Independent Sector Conference 10/23-25/1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - AEO Conference 4/22-25/1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - AEO Conference 4/22-25/1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives packet (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Putney School Campaign 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Council on Foundations 4/27-29/1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Trip - British Isles 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - AEO Trip 5/19-23/1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Management & Community Development Institute 6/1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Council on Foundations Conference 4/26-28/1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Conference Call 8/23/1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N Conference 5/7-9/1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N Administrative Memoranda, etc. 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N Research (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N Program (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N Board Nominations 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N Board/Executive Committee Administration (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N FOA Committee 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ALF/N Other Proposals (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - ALF/N General Fundraising (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - ALF/N Innovation Associates packet (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Boston (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - ALF/N Fleishman 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Northwest Area Foundation Annual Report 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - ALF/N CLIA (Collaborative Leadership in Action Initiative) Advisory Committee 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - ALF/N CLIA Conference 5/1-4/1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - ALF/N CLIA Fundraising Mott Foundation (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - ALF/N CLIA Fundraising Fannie Mae (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ALF/N CLIA Fundraising McCown, George (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ALF/N CLIA Fundraising (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - ALF/N CLIA General Grant Proposals (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - ALF/N CLIA Post Roundtable (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - ALF/N Advisory Committee Conference Call 2/17/1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - ALF/N packet (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - ALF/N Theorists 7/1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - ALF/N Facilities 1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - ALF/N Community Team Referrals (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - ALF/N Teams Memoranda (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - ALF/N Teams applications (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - ALF/N Executive Committee Strategic Planning Meeting 10/22-23/1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ALF/N Irvine Foundation Proposal (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - ALF/N Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Irvine Foundation (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ALF/N Conference 5/103/1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ALF/N Directory, etc. 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Women & Philanthropy 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Academy of Leadership packet 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Appalachian Center for Economic Networks packet 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Women's Pages 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - CWED (Coalition for Women's Economic Development) packets (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CWED Conference 6/29/1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Publications re: Women, Finance (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Microenterprise General 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Coalition of Community Funds for Youth (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Collaboration in Action (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Wilkinson, Ray (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Libraries To Go (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Council for Economic Development (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Council for Economic Development - Sherridan piece (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Northern California Community Loan Fund (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - OECD (Organization for Economic Cooperation & Development) 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - OEF (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Ontario Social Development 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Resources for Individual Entrepreneurs (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Revolving Loan Funds (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Rural Economic Assistance Project (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Shell UK (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Women's Business Network (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - WEDC (Women's Economic Development Corporation) 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Agency for International Development (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Women's Business Development (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Women's Economic Growth (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Rosenberg Foundation Board Meeting 4/26/1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rosenberg Foundation Board Meeting 4/25/1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Rosenberg Foundation Board Meeting 4/30/1996 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Rosenberg Foundation Board Meeting 4/27/1999 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - National Coalition for Women's Enterprise Post-closing Finance 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - HUB (HUB Co-Ventures for Women's Enterprise) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - HUB kits 1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - National Strategy Session on Women's Self-Employment 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - WEDA Briefing 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - HUB briefing (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - House Committee on Small Business (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Drucker Foundation (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - AEO 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Pegasus Communications packet (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, Reports (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Systems Thinking in Action Conference 10/3/1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Photographs 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Who's Who in the West 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Independent Sector packet 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Principles & Practices of Financial Management (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ms. Foundation (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Silicon Valley Business & Leadership Conference 5/26/1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Women & Philanthropy Conference 4/30/1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - IRWG (Institute for Research on Women & Gender) packet 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - AEO Conference 5/17-20/1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Global Fund for Women 1994 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Committee 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Current Prospects 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Corporate Associates Program (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Allday (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Amex (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Berkshire Hathaway (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Bins (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ALF/N Fundraising BP America (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Browning-Ferris (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Casey Foundation (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Chevron (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Commonwealth Fund (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Connecticut Mutual (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Dayton Hudson (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Ford (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Hanson (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Hewlett (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - ALF/N Fundraising IBM (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ALF/N Fundraising ITT (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Jaworski (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Johnson (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Kauffman Foundation (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Correspondence 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Kellogg (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Kidder & Peabody (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Luce (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - ALF/N Fundraising McCown (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - ALF/N Fundraising MacArthur (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Merrill Lynch (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Mertz-Gilmore (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Mott (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Packard (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Paine Webber (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Peninsula Community Foundation (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Pew (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Prudential (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Pfizer (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Rockefeller (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Rouse (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Shaler Adams (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Shearson Lehman Brothers (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Shell (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Smith Barres (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Surdna (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Tenneco (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Tides (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Time Warner (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - ALF/N Fundraising United Airlines (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - ALF/N Fundraising U.S. West (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Weintz (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Westinghouse (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Weyerhaeuser (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Xerox (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Board List (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Audit 1990 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Budget (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Chapter Models (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Contributors Report 1980-1995 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - ALF/N Fundraising 501(c)(3) (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Chapter Projects (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Overview (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Research Conclusions (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Bill Gomez (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Brochure Draft (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Information Piece (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Carolyn Barnes (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - ALF/N Fundraising Board (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - ALF/N Patrick (Consultant) (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - ALF/N Public Relations 1991 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - ALF/N Chapter Agreements (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - ALF/N Women, Leadership & the Future (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - ALF/N Chapter Executive Directors (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - ALF/N Executive Director Meeting 11/20-22/1999 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - ALF/N Antioch- Lang (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - ALF/N Aspen Institute (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Enterprise Foundation 10/1993 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Enterprise Foundation Rouse Visit 2/1991 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 4/4/1991 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee 1991 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 10/3/1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Foundation Denver Assessment 7/1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Foundation Charleston 4/1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Foundation Sante Fe 5/1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/23/1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/14/1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Foundation Articles, Correspondence, Notes, Photographs 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation Professional & Businesswomen's Conference 5/6/1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Foundation Fannie Mae National Housing survey 6/1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation National Center for Lead-Safe Housing (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Foundation Technical Assistance to Community Housing Development Organizations 6/30/1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Foundation St. Louis Draft 1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation Midland, Texas 5/1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Foundation Factors Affecting the Low Income Housing Industry (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 10/30/1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee 10/30/1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Enterprise Foundation Conference 10/29-30/1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Foundation Annual Report 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Enterprise Foundation Hope from Homes (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Enterprise Foundation Press 1992 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 4/9/1992 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Colorado 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Flint, Michigan (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Portland, Maine (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Philadelphia (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Worcester, Massachusetts (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development Yakima Valley, Washington (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - ALF/N People's Resources (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - ALF/N Inquiries (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - ALF/N National Directory 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - ALF/N Brochure (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - ALF/N Report, Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Union Institute packet (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Union Institute- Mark Rosenman (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/23/1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Foundation Executive Committee & Financial Review & Audit Committee Combined Meeting 10/1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Foundation Strategic Plan 1995-2000 10/1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 10/26/1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Foundation Making Communities Safe 10/28/1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Foundation What Ought to Be Can Be 10/26-28/1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/23/1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation Executive Committee & Financial Review & Audit Committee Combined Meeting (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Y2K 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Women's World Banking (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - National Committee on Working Women (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Women's Institute for Housing & Economic Development (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Women, Leadership & the Future (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Women's Research & Educational Institute (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Women's Wire packet (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Leadership America 1995 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Correspondence, Notes, Publications 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Trip- Manchester 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - YWCA (YWCA Mid-Peninsula Women Entrepreneurs Program) 1994 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Publications 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Independent Sector 1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Presentation Material 2/7/1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Rural Strategies (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Rimonte Reprint & Correspondence 1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Womancare packet (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Bay Area Discovery Museum packet (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - ACC International Institute (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Clever, Linda 1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - National Civic League - America's Future Conference 9/22-23/1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Putney School (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ALF 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Peninsula Community Foundation 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Leadership California 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mid-Peninsula Citizens for Fair Housing packet (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Publications, Articles (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Notes, Memoranda (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Foundation Financial Review & Audit Committee Meeting 1/1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/20/1994 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Foundation Social Investment 1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 1/1/1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Foundation Community Service Task Force 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Foundation 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 10/7/1993 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Enterprise Foundation Board Meeting 7/1/1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Enterprise Foundation Trip 7/1/1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Enterprise Foundation Lead-Based Paint Hazards (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - IRWG Advisory Committee (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - IRWG 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Working Assets Holdings 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Fannie Mae Advisory Committee Trip 4/10-11/1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Joint Venture Silicon Valley Index 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Anne Dunbar (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - ALF/N General (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - ALF/N Coordinator (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ALF/N Chapter Development (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ALF/N Board Meeting 5/1-5/1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)